<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Car &#8211; Ambrosia Botanicals | Perfumes | Tea</title>
	<atom:link href="https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals/product-category/toy/car/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals</link>
	<description>PAN India Delivery</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:55:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AB-site-logo.png</url>
	<title>Car &#8211; Ambrosia Botanicals | Perfumes | Tea</title>
	<link>https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Remote Control Car</title>
		<link>https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals/product/remote-control-car/</link>
					<comments>https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals/product/remote-control-car/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DabRah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals/?post_type=product#038;p=105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">Assembly Required: Yes
Batteries Required: Yes
Batteries Included: Yes
tech_spec_battery_description_toys: ‎Lithium-Ion
Material Type(s): Plastic
Colour: White, Black, Red</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4 class="a-size-base-plus a-text-bold">About this item</h4>
<ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini">
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">【APP RC Cars】Containing 3686 bricks, after the assembly of this remote control car building blocks, you can not only control the movement of the vehicle through the remote control handle but also through the mobile phone APP, which is easy to operate. 2.4GHZ remote control, the signal is stable, and the remote control distance is farther than 65.61 feet. Four doors of the off-road vehicle, the hood, and the bucket door can all be opened, which highly restores the real car structure.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">【Multifunctional Car】Our model car kits are equipped with off-road tires, and the suspension above the wheels simulates a shock-absorbing structure that is not afraid of bumps. 1 servo motor and 2 monster motors can provide enough power for the vehicle to conquer all kinds of terrain. These RC cars can go forward, backward, turn left, turn right, you can make it rotate 360°in place and enjoy the fun of manipulation. This is an advanced off-road vehicle model specially designed for car enthusiasts.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">【Enjoy Building】The design of this car is close to the real model, giving technology enthusiasts a more realistic experience, focus and enjoy this challenging building process! The surface of our building toys particles is round and does not easy to hurt hands. Not only a building block ornament but also a car that can be controlled and driven. RC car kits to build has multiple ways to play and are equipped with a rechargeable battery, which can last for 15-20 minutes after charging for 2-3 hours.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">【Ideal Gifts】Packaged in a premium black gift box with a detailed instruction manual, this remote control truck is a great gift for building block enthusiasts and tech enthusiasts! This set includes high-performance motors, a rechargeable 550mAh lithium battery, a USB charging cable, remote control (battery not included, 2 AAA batteries required). Model cars have both texture and beauty, are very domineering, and are worthy of collection. It will be a perfect birthday, Christmas, or anniversary gift idea.</span></li>
<li class="a-spacing-mini"><span class="a-list-item">【Always at Your Service】The finished model measures 22.9in(L)x9.5in(W)x8.9in(H). Our model building kits come in numbered bags for easy assembly. Before the product is packaged, it goes through several checks to ensure the integrity of the parts. If you find some parts are missing during the building process, please contact us and we will reissue them for you as soon as possible. Whatever problem you have, JMBricklayer team will do our best to solve it.</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dabrah123.github.io/Ambrosia-Botanicals/product/remote-control-car/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">105</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
